LOGAN COLLINS

Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

+1-516-654-4426

@ hermes8527@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

Brewlahs

= 04/2023 - 03/2024

Phttps://brewlabs.info/

- Created the company landing page using React from the Figma design, featuring simple yet elegant components and smooth animations
- Created UI kit and unit test script to expedite front-end development for landing pages and on-chain services such as staking
- Developed Smart Contract, wrote unit tests and integrated Web3 in Staking and Zap-In functions
- Collaborated with company executives to improve performance and service utilities and expand community

Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

SparkWorld*

= 04/2022 - 03/2023

- Collaborated with the CTO to clarify main features of NFT Marketplace and
- Developed Smart Contract of NFT Marketplace and wrote unit test scripts in Hardhat framework
- Fixed several security and performance issues and passed smart contract audit
- Developed a bot to get NFT sale data and metadata from other NFT Marketplaces on Avalanche and store them in MongoDB as a subproject of NFT Aggregator

Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

Satang Technologies

= 04/2020 - 03/2022

https://satang.com/

- Collaborated with a designer to create a modern, yet simple user interface for our company's landing page
- Designed and developed Firo Bridge to synchronize data between the Firo chain and FiroVM chain and store transaction data in PostgreSQL database to enable Smart Contracts on Firo like Ethereum
- Designed the workflow and developed Smart Contract, front-end, back-end and integrated Web3 to utilize real-estate transactions on the blockchain

Senior Full Stack Developer

Polisport

= 04/2019 - 03/2020

https://polisport.com/, https://polisportvirtualtour.com/

- Joined the company as a Full Stack Web Developer
- Collaborated with backend developers to retrieve products and services data for implementation of a pixel-perfect frontend in React from Figma
- Wrote unit test scripts for the front-end using Mocha and Jest libraries
- Led Polisport Virtual Tour Project and implemented main UI in React and virtual tour in 3d environment using Three.js library

Full Stack Developer

Canary Technologies

= 04/2016 - 03/2019

https://glassbororentals.com/, https://ventano.de/

- During my six-month internship as a developer, I gained valuable insights into the company's culture and development methodologies
- In the Glassboro Rentals project, I created smooth and visually appealing user interfaces as a front-end developer
- Designed MySQL database and contributed to three pages using Laravel framework as a Full Stack Developer in the Ventano project

SUMMARY

A seasoned full-stack blockchain developer with 8+ years of experience in the web development industry.

Stepped into the blockchain industry as a Smart Contract and Web3 developer in 2018.

What sets me apart is the ability to learn new technologies, passion for the product and keen eye for detail.

I always create detailed workflows, progress stepby-step, and conduct thorough testing to ensure accuracy and timely development.

I enjoy proposing new ideas, wearing different hats, and collaborating with others to achieve success.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science

GPA

DePaul Unversity = 2012 - 2016

Ohicago, IL

3.9 / 4.0

SKILLS

Solidity	Ethereum	Smart Contract	
Hardhat	Foundry	Web3	Ethers.js
Front-end			
React	/ue Typ	eScript	Lit
Back-end			
Node.js	Golang	Laravel	
Database			
MongoDB	MySQL	Postgr	eSQL
Developme	nt & Operat	tions	
Scrum	Agile		

GitLab

Microsoft Azure

Bitbucket

Version Control Systems

GitHub

GCP

Cloud Services

Git

AWS